tweeter.com 2007-10-11

# Tweeter - Privacy Policy

We at Tweeter, producers of Tweeter.com, believe that you have the right to know how your personal information may be used or disclosed. You take your privacy seriously, and we respect your concerns. We have created this privacy policy in order to educate you as to as to how we collect information, what we do with it, and what controls you have. Please read it carefully, and if you have any questions or concerns, please send us a comment at [customersupport@tweeter.com](mailto:customersupport@tweeter.com?%20subject=Privacy%20Policy%20Questions) or contact us by telephone at 1-800-TWEETER.

This privacy policy applies only to personal information collected via this website, and not to any other activities of Tweeter or its affiliates or business partners. Personal information means information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, e-mail address, phone number, or credit card information, and that is not otherwise publicly available. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Tweeter does not own or control, or to people that Tweeter does not employ or manage, except as set forth below.

**Information Collection and Use**

**Information**  
When visiting any Web site, your browser sends information to the site's hosting server identifying the browser you are using, your Internet Service Provider, the page you last visited, and the page you are currently visiting. We log this information and we may also track and catalog the search terms that you enter in our search forms. When you purchase a product on Tweeter.com, we ask you for the following information: name address, phone number, e-mail address and credit card and expiration date. We may also receive information from you in connection with contests or sweepstakes on Tweeter.com, customer feedback you provide, and customer service help you request. 

We use information to administer and improve Tweeter.com, process and follow up on your order, and contact you.

**Cookies**  
We make use of a standard feature of browser software called a "cookie" to that helps us recognize you when you visit. Cookies allow us to recognize you when you pay a repeat visit to Tweeter.com. Cookies let us personalize your shopping experience based on your preferences and help Tweeter.com to work better. 

Most browsers accept cookies. However, if you wish, you can usually set your browser to refuse cookies. If you set your browser to refuse cookies, you may not be able to submit an order online. Tweeter does not use cookies to gather any personal information.

**About Children**  
For their protection, we ask that children under age 13 do not submit information to us without the consent of a parent or guardian. Tweeter will not intentionally contact children under age 13 about special offers or for marketing purposes without a parent's permission. We do not collect any personally identifiable information from anyone whom we know to be under the age of 13, nor do we sell or ship any items directly to anyone whom we know to be under the age of 18.

**Security**  
We use industry-standard SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption technology, a secure server, and other physical and procedural safeguards to protect the security of your personal information. Please understand, however, that no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our databases, nor can we guarantee that the information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet. Please keep your password private. We will never ask for it by phone or e-mail, and neither should anyone else.

**Disclosure of Personal Information**  
Tweeter does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 

  * We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Tweeter under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help Tweeter fulfill orders, process credit card payment, evaluate Tweeter.com or communicate with you about offers from Tweeter and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information. You may opt out of future marketing communications from Tweeter or our marketing partners at any time by e-mailing to [customersupport@tweeter.com](mailto:customersupport@tweeter.com?%20subject=Privacy%20Policy%20Questions) or calling us at 1-800-TWEETER. 
  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. 
  * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of the Tweeter.com terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 
  * We transfer information about you if Tweeter is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Tweeter will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. **Please note that on July 13, 2007, the U.S. Bankruptcy Court for the District of Delaware (in case no. 07-10787 PJW) authorized the sale of the Tweeter businesses to new owners.   The new owners have adopted all of Tweeter's existing privacy policies.  As a result, all customer information will remain protected by Tweeter's existing privacy policies. **

**3rd Parties/Links**  
Tweeter.com contains links to other websites. Please recognize that we cannot control the use or security of your personal information collected by other websites. If you have any concerns regarding the security or privacy of these websites, you should feel free to browse their privacy policies, or even to contact them directly. Tweeter is not responsible for the privacy practices, data collection, security or content of other websites.

**Correcting, Updating and Removing Your Personal Information**  
If you wish to correct, update or remove any personal information that you have provided through Tweeter.com, please email us at [customersupport@tweeter.com](mailto:customersupport@tweeter.com?%20subject=Privacy%20Policy%20Questions) or contact us by telephone at 1-800-TWEETER.

**Your Consent and Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
By using Tweeter.com, you consent to the collection and use of your information as we have outlined in this privacy policy. If you do not agree to our policy, you may not use Tweeter.com. We may change this privacy policy at any time and without prior notice. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to an e-mail address you have provided to us or by placing a prominent notice on Tweeter.com so that you may be aware of our actions. Your continued use of Tweeter.com following any such notice will mean that you accept such changes.
